Guide to the Everett Needham Case papers A1015
Special Collections and University Archives, Colgate University Libraries
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: W.W. Trench., 1942 December 10 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Pulling., 1942 December 31 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Thomas S. Matthews., 1944 January 5 (Box 11, Folder 1, Box 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Robert Hunter., 1944 January 5 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1944 January 5 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Burnham Carter., 1944 January 5 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson, Jr., 1944 January 7 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mary Hinckley Dearing., 1944 January 7 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John P. Young., 1944 January 31 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.R. de la Torre Bueno, Jr., 1944 February 12 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: C.D. Williams., 1944 February 12 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Verse. Case, Everett N. "Triolet Imperfect.", 1944 February 14 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1944 March 9 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Lovell Thompson., 1944 March 13 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Robert C. Roberts., 1944 March 20 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Serena Savage., 1944 March 27 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George Cooley., 1944 March 31 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Charles L. Raper., 1944 April 5 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Robert Buechner., 1944 April 28 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Stuart Crocker., 1944 May 3 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Stuart Crocker., 1944 May 10 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Forrestal., 1944 May 11 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Norman MacKenzie., 1944 May 25 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George D. Stoddard., 1944 May 26 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Chalfant Robinson., 1944 June 1 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Charles Shipway., 1944 June 1 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Walter A. Jessup., 1944 June 10 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Matthew Griswold., 1944 June 10 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Matthew Griswold., 1944 June 19 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1944 June 26 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Clyde Sparling., 1944 August 16 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Allan V. Heely., 1944 August 18 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Erdman Harris., 1944 August 18 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Thomas Carroll., 1944 August 19 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James M. Mead., 1944 August 19 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Allan Heely., 1944 August 31 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Niles Trammell., 1944 September 1 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1944 September 2 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1944 September 2 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Dorothy Thomas., 1944 September 16 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Dorothy Thomas., 1944 September 23 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Ethel Stark., 1944 September 16 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Niles Trammell., 1944 September 16 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Irving S. Wright., 1944 September 21 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Chalfant Robinson., 1944 September 27 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J. Delafield DuBois., 1944 September 28 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James M. Mead., 1944 September 30 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Keith Kane, 1944 October 26 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Olivia Hatch., 1944 November 1 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Hamilton Robinson., 1944 November 3 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Young., 1944 November 3 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: T.K. Drummond., 1944 November 6 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Lillian V. Morrison., 1944 November 20 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: W.E. Stevenson., 1944 November 27 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward R. Stettinius, Jr., 1944 November 20 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Harvey L. Williams., 1944 December 1 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: T.M. Greene., 1944 December 5 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Lovell Thompson., 1944 December 5 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Louis Hyde, Jr., 1944 December 5 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Russell Davenport., 1944 December 5 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- TL, signed. Case, Everett N. To: John Young., 1944 December 6 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.D. DuBois., 1944 December 7 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Irving S. Wright., 1944 December 18 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: N.A.M. McKenzie., 1944 December 18 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: F. Vinton Lawrence, Jr., 1944 December 20 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. John Baker., 1950 January 31 (Box 12, Folder 1, Box 13)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Dr. E.E. Day., 1950 February 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Theodore Greene., 1950 February 11 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: David Carter., 1950 February 15 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Bernard Samuels., 1950 February 15 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To; J.M. Beiermeister., 1950 February 24 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Herbert Williams., 1950 February 24 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Charles Scott., 1950 February 28 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Peter Garvan., 1950 March 20 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Allan Heely., 1950 March 31 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Allen Heely., 1950 March 31 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.M. Beiermeister., 1950 April 1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Walter Edmonds., 1950 April 1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: W.S.A. Pott., 1950 April 3 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.M. Beiermeister., 1950 April 10 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Louis Hyde, Jr., 1950 April 11 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H. Alexander Smith., 1950 April 12 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Alan Valentine., 1950 April 12 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Dr. Ashe., 1950 April 14 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Christian Gauss., 1950 April 17 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Meta Glass., 1950 April 17 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Louis Hyde, Jr., 1950 April 22 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frederic Foord., 1950 April 27 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. William Stevenson., 1950 April 28 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Theodore Greene., 1950 May 1 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Reed., 1950 May 16 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Young., 1950 May 24 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Telegram. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Young., 1950 May 24 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Dr. Harold Dodds., 1950 May 25 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Louis Hyde, Jr., 1950 May 25 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Stanley King., 1950 June 5 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Hancock., 1950 June 6 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Read., 1950 June 6 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. to: John Neilson., 1950 June 8 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Neilson., 1950 June 8 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Thomas Matthews., 1950 June 21 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Alison Carter., 1950 June 27 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: E.E. Day., 1950 July 26 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Alexander Phinney., 1950 September 27 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Philip Young., 1950 October 11 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Alan Valentine., 1950 October 11 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Eleanor Edmonds., 1950 October 18 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Irving S. Wright., 1950 October 19 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mary Atwater., 1950 October 19 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Malcolm Rowe., 1950 November 1 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: William Hard., 1950 November 1 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Thomas H. Carroll., 1950 November 11 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Pulling., 1950 November 24 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Charles Young., 1950 November 29 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Clarence Woolley., 1950 December 9 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Myers., 1950 December 18 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Robert Lehman., 1963 December 11 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John G. Winslow., 1963 December 11 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1963 December 11 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John G. Winslow., 1963 December 27 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. J.H. Case., 1947 July 7 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. J.H. Case., 1947 November 19 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- TL, signed. Case, Everett N. To: Robert Woods., 1982 March 25 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- TL, signed. Case, Everett N. To: Robert Wood., 1982 January 26 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Henry D. West., 1964 January 28 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward L. Sibert, Jr., 1966 March 25 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Arthur F. Burns., 1967 December 22 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Arthur F. Burns., 1966 January 21 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Herman Brautigam., 1968 April 22 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Holbert Carroll., 1967 July 10 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: S. Cole Blasier., 1964 June 17 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George W. Ball., 1968 April 2 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case, 1949 February 3 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1949 February 25 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Raymond Rubicam., 1949 May 15 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John P. Meyers., 1949 May 20 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1949 June 15 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Theodore Greene., 1949 June 15 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1949 June 24 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- TL, signed. Case, Everett N. To: Clarence Wooley., 1949 June 25 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1949 June 25 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. J.H. Case., 1948 July 7 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1949 February 15 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1949 June 22 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Neills., 1948 August 20 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John P. Young., 1949 May 15 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1964 November 4 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Lessie Cherry., 1964 December 21 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Charles H. Brower., 1965 January 6 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Robert Lehman., 1965 January 18 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1965 February 18 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Ellen & Virginia Murray., 1965 February 11 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Dr. Harold S. Yood., 1965 March 8 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Burlington., 1965 March 28 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George Grandi., 1965 April 5 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1965 May 7 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1965 June 21 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: George F. Grandi., 1965 June 21 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Anna Jelmert., 1965 August 24 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: R.W. McFall., 1965 September 20 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Marta Forssen., 1965 September 22 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Glenn E. Hanneman., 1966 April 6 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Marta Forssen., 1966September 20 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1966 October 17 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Robert Lehman., 1966 December 28 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Monroe C. Gutman., 1966 December 28 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Rathbone., 1945 July 21 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1945 October 13 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Parents., 1945 November 12 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1945 December 20 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Dr. Gardner., 1963 April 11 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1963 May 3 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1963 June 27 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1963 July 15 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.H. Case., 1963 September 23 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Katherine Farris., 1963 November 22 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John C. Baker., 1939 June 27 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Patch., 1939 June 28 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John C. Baker., 1939 June 28 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: St. George Sioussat., 1939 June 28 (Box 14, Folder 64)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John C. Baker., 1939 July 6 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John C. Baker., 1939 July 14 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Arthur Cole., 1939 July 14 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Patch., 1939 July 14 (Box 14, Folder 68)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John H. Williams., 1939 August 10 (Box 14, Folder 69)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Patch., 1939 August 13 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Arthur Cole., 1939 August 19 (Box 14, Folder 71)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John Williams., 1939 August 19 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Patch., 1939 August 20 (Box 14, Folder 73)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Alan Valentine., 1948 July 13 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Lawrence Terry., 1948 November 20 (Box 14, Folder 75)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Francis Spaulding., 1948 July 22 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Nathaniel Stevens., 1948 July 14 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- Telegram. Case, Everett N. To: Adlai Stevenson., 1948 November 2 (Box 14, Folder 78)
- TN, signed. Stevenson, Adlai. To: Everett N. Case., 1948 November 7 (Box 14, Folder 79)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Adlai Stevenson., 1948 December 15 (Box 14, Folder 80)
- TN, signed. Case, Everett N. To: Everett N. Case., 1948 December 22 (Box 14, Folder 81)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Durand Rice., 1949 May 23 (Box 14, Folder 82)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Frederic Rope., 1949 May 2 (Box 14, Folder 83)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Leonabel Jacobs., 1949 January 4 (Box 14, Folder 84)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: John B. Johnson., 1949 May 30 (Box 14, Folder 85)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Edward Watts, Jr., 1949 February 24 (Box 14, Folder 86)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: J.D. Hatch, Jr., 1949 March 14 (Box 14, Folder 87)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H.H. Hackney., 1949 May 31 (Box 14, Folder 88)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: H.H. Hackney., 1949 June 28 (Box 14, Folder 89)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Raymond Fosdick., 1948September 8 (Box 14, Folder 90)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1941 May 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1941 October 24 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1941 October 27 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1942 January 8 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1942 March 9 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1942 June 26 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1942 October 24 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1942 December 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1943 April 28 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1943 May 17 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1943 June 3 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1943 June 10 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1943 June 17 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1943 July 26 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1943 September 3 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1943 September 22 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1943 November 8 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1943 November 22 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1944 May 26 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1944 September 23 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1944 August 15 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1944 November 3 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1944 November 30 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1944 December 11 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1945 January 5 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1945 January 17 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1945 March 1 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- TL,unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1945 May 23 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1945 June 7 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1945 June 11 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: James Case., 1945 June 15 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Owen D. Young., 1924-1934 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Owen D. Young and E.W.R. Correspondence., 1913 March (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Everett Needham Case and Owen D. Young Correspondence., 1935-1973 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Case, Everett N. "Footnotes to Freedom: The American Idea.", 1949 September 23 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- James H. Case, Jr., Herbert N. Couch, Charles A. Robinson, Jr. "The Liberal Arts Curriculum.", 1943 March 18 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Case, Everett N. "A New Approach to Social Sciences.", 1948 October 8 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Case, Everett N. "Report of Everett Case, President of Colgate University.", 1944 February 19 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- TN, signed. Case, Everett N. To: Charles Hanne., 1933 January 5 (Box 16, Folder 1, Box 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case,Everett N. To: Whom It May Concern., 1943 December 3 (Box 16, Folder 2, Box 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. Howard Case., 1949 January 25 (Box 16, Folder 3, Box 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. Howard Case, 1949 February 16 (Box 16, Folder 4, Box 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Howard Case., 1948 September 3 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Howard Case., 1948 September 15 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Samuel Case., 1948 September 15 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Howard Case., 1953 July 16 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. Howard Case., 1953 January 14 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Howard Case., 1952 December 30 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mr. & Mrs. Howard Case., 1951 February 21 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. Howard Case., 1951 October 1 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Howard Case., 1950 February 16 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Elizabeth Case., 1950 February 1 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Telegram. Case, Josephine. To: Everett N. Case., 1944 January (Box 16, Folder 15)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Willard Case., 1945 January 27 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Pauline Needham., 1946 May 29 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Pauline Needham., 1946 March 25 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Case, Everett N. "Nature Rhymes: The Moth.", undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Case, Everett N. Valentine Poem., 1944 February 14 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Susan Parker Case., 1944 November 29 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Mrs. John C. McLaughlin., 1944 October 26 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Pauline Needham., 1944 January 5 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- TN, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Willard Case., 1942 January 21 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- TL, unsigned. Case, Everett N. To: Howard M. Case., 1943 January 19 (Box 16, Folder 25)